http://www.cuveecoffee.com/pages/privacy-policy

Skip to content
BUY COFFEEFIND CUVEEBUY GEARABOUTROASTERYCOLD BREWERYCOFFEE BARCONTACTCLEARANCE
Account
Cart
Your cart is empty
FREE SHIPPING OVER $25!
Privacy Policy
Get familiar with our policies and terms.
Thank you for visiting Cuvée Coffee, LLC (also referred to as “we,” “us,” and “our”) website.
We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we want to keep your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy describes our information practices. By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy before you submit any personal information on this website.
What information about customers do we gather?
Personal information
To simply browse our website, we do not ask you to provide any personal information.
However, if you wish to participate in many of the features and services offered on our website, we may ask you to provide certain personally identifiable and/or demographic information.
Personally identifiable information, as used in this Privacy Policy, refers to any information that can be used to personally identify you or contact you.
This may include, for example, your name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number, as well as demographic information that is linked to personally identifiable information.
Demographic information, as used in this Privacy Policy, refers to information that describes personal characteristics but could not, on its own, be used to personally identify you or contact you.
Demographic information may include your date of birth, age, gender, habits, or preferences.
Personally identifiable information and/or demographic information are only collected when you voluntarily provide it to us through one of the online forms available on this website, which may be most commonly encountered when:
purchasing products or services from this website;
registering or signing up for membership on this website;
posting comments on message boards and other interactive discussion forms;
responding to surveys;
participating in sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions;
registering for newsletters or other communications from us; or
any other interaction that requires the submission of personal information.
If demographic information is collected for an activity or service that also requires personally identifiable information, we may combine the demographic information with your personally identifiable information.
Combining this data allows us to customize the notices we send you and the content we provide you according to your interests and preferences.
Non-personal information
Cookies
We use cookies to improve the use and functionality of our website.
A cookie is a small file that websites often store on a user’s computer.
Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient way for us to personalize or enhance your experience on our website and to make your next visit more enjoyable.
For example, cookies may allow us to remember the content you previously viewed on our website or your log-in information.
Cookies may also be used to remember items you have previously placed in your shopping cart when making purchases.
We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information, however we may link information contained in a cookie to personally identifiable information collected from you by other means (e.g., website registration).
You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.
The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, if you do so, you may not be able to register on our website or use other features that require registration or the collection of information.
IP Addresses
We may keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to, among other things:
(i) troubleshoot technical concerns; (ii) maintain website safety and security; (iii) restrict access to our website to certain users; and (iv) better understand how our website is utilized.
An IP address is a number used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.
Log Files
We, or a vendor on our behalf, may collect information in the form of logs, files that record website activity and gather statistics about web users’ browsing habits.
These entries are generated anonymously and help us gather, among other things:
(i) a user’s browser type and operating system; (ii) information about a user’s session (such as the URL they came from, the date and time they visited our website, and which pages they have viewed on our site and for how long); and (iii) other similar navigational data.
We may also use information captured in log files for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve and customize the online services we provide you.
Log files are used internally only and are not associated with any particular user.
Web Beacons
We may use web beacons on our website or include them in e-mail messages we send you.
Web beacons are small strings of programming code that provide a method of delivering a graphic image on a web page or e-mail message for the purposes of transferring data back to us.
Web beacons may be used to allow us, or our advertising delivery partners, to communicate with cookies stored on your computer.
The information collected via web beacons may also include some of the information described in the IP Address section above, as well as information about how a user responds to an e-mail campaign (such as, the time the e-mail is opened, where does the user link to from the e-mail, etc.).
We use web beacon information for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to, site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising and e-mail auditing and reporting, and content personalization.
How do we use the information we collect?
Generally, all information collected is used for the purpose for which the information was collected or as otherwise identified at the point of collection or in this Privacy Policy.
For example, if you register or open an account on this website, the information you provide may be used to offer you the benefits and privileges that typically come along with registration.
This may include purchasing products and/or services, access to and use of exclusive or personalized content or activities (such as message boards), participation in special events and promotions (contests, sweepstakes, coupons, etc.), and the ability to receive any communications or marketing material you select at the time of registration or that automatically come with registration.
Similarly, if you contact us via an online contact form, your information may be used to respond to your inquiry or comment, and in some instances, post the answers to your question in anonymous form on the website.
Any credit card information you provide us is used to fulfill and process your online purchases.
When providing information on our website, you may also be given the option (through a check box or otherwise) to have your information used for an activity or service different from the primary activity or service that you are requesting.
For example, if you are signing up for a contest or other promotion, you may also be able to sign up for newsletters or alerts from this website or our partners.
If you choose to receive these additional services, we will use your information to provide them to you.
From time to time, we may be approached by reputable third party companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
To extend these products or services to you, we may use your personally identifiable information to send out notices on their behalf.
We see this as a value-added service helping you find useful products or services.
Our goal is to limit the notices and communications to those that we think you would appreciate receiving.
Please note that all such mailings come strictly from us and your personally identifiable information is not shared with these other companies.
We may also use your personal and/or demographic information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve, personalize, and customize the products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs.
This may include occasionally combining, updating, or otherwise enhancing the personally identifiable information collected through this website with data we receive from outside records or third parties.
The following provides additional information about certain features of our website.
Newsletters and E-mail
If you provide us your e-mail address and/or mailing address, the contact information you provide may be used to send you newsletters, product or service literature, or other communications that you request.
In addition, you may receive communications introducing you to other Nestlé brands or websites.
We may also use your e-mail address to send you transactional or administrative communications (e.g., confirmation e-mail when you make an online purchase or sign up for, or unsubscribe from, a service or activity), as well as certain service-related announcements.
Collectively, these types of communications are referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Administrative Communications.”
Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions
To enter an online sweepstakes, contest, or promotion (collectively “Promotions”), you may be required to first register on this website.
The information collected as part of a Promotion is used to determine your eligibility, notify you whether you are a winner, and/or fulfill and deliver prizes.
We may use third party service providers to operate sweepstakes.
In these instances, we may share the information collected for the Promotion with that third party, so that it may perform tasks necessary to provide the sweepstakes.
If you are a winner, certain information about you
(such as your name and picture) may be posted to the website.
For more information about Promotions, please see the official rules or details posted with a specific Promotion.
Surveys
There are two types of surveys that may be conducted on this website.
One is where purely demographic or survey information (such as age, gender, household information, and other interests, etc.) is requested and the information is not linked to any personally identifiable information about you.
In other cases (such as during website registration), we may collect the same information and combine it with your personally identifiable information.
Message Boards and other interactive features
Visitors may post reviews, comments, and other content; send e-cards and other communications; and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions, or other information, so long as the content is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of “Spam”. You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of a card or other content. We reserve the right (but do not have the obligation) to remove or edit such content, but do not regularly review posted content.
We encourage you to be wary of giving out personally identifiable information or images about yourself in public areas such as on a message board or other online community feature.
Such information can be collected and used by people you do not know.
As such, we cannot guarantee the security and privacy of, and are not responsible for, any information you post in these areas.
Your use of these features is at your own risk.
Please note that if you choose to post a picture or message through one of these features, we may post, along with the picture or message, certain non-personally identifiable information about you, such as your username and/or city and state of residence.
If you do post content or submit material, you grant us and our affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. You grant us and our affiliates and sublicensees the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content, if they choose. You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify
Cuvée Coffee, LLC or its affiliates for all claims resulting from content you supply.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any content posted by you or any third party.
This website may also provide one-time use interactive features, such as e-cards and tell-a-friend messages.
Personally identifiable information requested for an e-card, tell-a-friend message, or other referral feature, or other one-time use features (typically, e-mail addresses and names) will be used on a one-time basis (e.g., to send the communication) and will not be further retained by Cuvée Coffee.
Purchasing Products and Services Online
This website may allow you to purchase Cuvée Coffee, LLC products or services through an online store operated by Cuvée Coffee, LLC or a vendor on our behalf, as well as provide links to unaffiliated third-party sites that sell Cuvée Coffee products.
If you are purchasing a product or service through a Cuvée Coffee, LLC website, you will be asked to provide your credit card information, including credit card number and billing and shipping addresses, as well as other basic contact information (e.g., telephone number and e-mail address).
This information is used to fulfill your purchase and confirm your order.
If the online store you are visiting is operated by an unaffiliated third party, we may provide you a direct link to the third party store for your convenience.
Please note, however, that these sites are not operated by Cuvée Coffee, LLC and are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
We encourage you to read the privacy policy of the online store you are visiting before sharing any personally identifiable information or sensitive information such as your credit card number.
Who is collecting your information and is it shared with anyone?
The information that you disclose on this website is collected by Cuvée Coffee, LLC or by a vendor acting on its behalf; and is used in accordance with the practices set forth above.
The following provides more specific information about how and to whom we may disclose your information.
Agents and Contractors
We may use outside companies, agents, or contractors (collectively “vendors”) to provide support for the internal operations of our websites and to assist us with administering e-commerce services or various other programs and promotions available on our website.
Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payment and providing customer service. In the course of doing so, these vendors may come into contact with your personal information.
However, we only give them access to (or allow them to collect on our behalf) the information they need in order to perform the specific tasks they have been hired to do.
They may not use it for other purposes.
Third Party Ad Networks
This site may utilize third party web beacons to help manage online advertising.
These web beacons are provided by our advertising delivery partners.
These pixels enable our partners to recognize a unique cookie on your computer, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website as well as provide you with targeted advertisements.
The information we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address.
For more information regarding third party web beacons and cookies or to opt out of targeted advertisements delivered by our advertising delivery partners, go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Partners, Affiliates and Joint Promotions
From time to time, we may run a joint or co-sponsored program or promotion on our websites with another company, organization, affiliate or other reputable third party; and, as part of this event, collect and process personally identifiable information.
You can tell when another company or business is involved in our promotions or your transactions and we may share customer information related to those transactions with that company or business. Periodically, we may run a promotion on our website that features the products or services of another company and may give you the opportunity to opt in to receive information directly from that third party company.
When operating any promotion involving another company, we may provide a separate link to that company’s website. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a company other than Cuvée Coffee, LLC Company, you can always choose not to opt in or participate in these events at the time the information is collected/ requested. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any of these businesses or individuals or the content of their websites.
We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, content of all these and any other third parties.
We encourage you to carefully review their privacy policies and other conditions of use.
Legal and Business Transfers
We may also disclose personally identifiable information if we are required to do so by law, or if in our good faith judgment, such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal processes, to respond to any claims, or to protect the safety or rights of Cuvée Coffee, its customers, or the public.
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets.
In such transactions, personally identifiable information generally is one of the transferred business assets.
Also, in the event of a merger or acquisition of all or part of Cuvée Coffee, LLC by another company, or in the event that
Cuvée Coffee, LLC were to sell or dispose of all or a part of Cuvée Coffee, LLC business, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by that business, which could include personally identifiable information, subject to applicable law.
Similarly, personally identifiable information may be transferred as part of a corporate reorganization, insolvency proceeding, or other similar event, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.
Aggregate Information
We may share aggregated demographic or survey information with third parties, but this information is in anonymous form and does not contain any personally identifiable information.
The aggregate information that we share may include anonymous information that is captured through the use of cookies and other similar tracking technology, as discussed in the Non-personal information section above.
What safeguards do we use to protect your personal information?
Cuvée Coffee, LLC takes commercially reasonable effects to protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information collected from our website visitors.
These efforts may include, but are not necessarily limited to:
(i) storing your personal information in secure operating environments; (ii) using industry standard SSL encryption to protect the security of certain sensitive personal information (such as credit card information) during transmission to our websites; and (iii) verifying the identities of registered website users before they can access the personal information we maintain about them.
If you use this site to access your online account, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password.
What choices do I have?
The following outlines the choices you have with respect to the collection and use of your personal information by Cuvée Coffee.
You always have the option not to share any of your personal information with us.
However, if you choose this option, you will be limited in the activities and features we can provide you.
If you do not want to receive newsletters, announcements, or other communications and/or services from this website, please opt out from these communications or services at the time of registration or when the information is collected.
If you have opted in and, at a later time, wish to opt out, you may update your profile on the website and amend your preferences or contact us at the address below.
Along with e-mail marketing communication sent to you, we will provide you the opportunity to discontinue receiving future marketing communications (i.e., unsubscribe).
Simply follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail.
You can always review or update any personal information that we may have collected about you for our general website registration by visiting the appropriate update profile sections of the website.
If any of the mechanisms set forth above is not available or you wish to make a different request, please contact as at:
Cuvée Coffee, LLC
22601 State Highway 71 W
Spicewood, TX 78669
Please note that regardless of your opt out selections, we reserve the right to continue sending you Administrative Communications if you have previously provided your information in connection with any one of our online features, activities, or services.
In addition, please note that if you participated in a promotion or program that involved a third party company and, as part of that promotion, you agreed to receive future communications directly from that third party, you will need to contact the third party (not Cuvée Coffee) directly to opt out from such communications.
This process may be outlined in the third party’s privacy policy.
Children
This website is a general audience website. We do not sell products for purchase by children or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should always get their parent’s or guardian’s consent before providing information to anyone via the Internet. If you are under the age of 13, you should not register or provide any information on our Web site. We do not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.
Terms and Conditions, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit our site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Texas, as set forth in our Terms and Conditions. If you have any concern about privacy on our site, please send us a thorough description to the address below and we will try to resolve it.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC
22601 State Highway 71 W
Spicewood, TX 78669
We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy.
Any changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy.
We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you come back to this website to make sure you are aware of any changes and how your information may be used.
Your continued use of this website signifies your acceptance of these changes.
Terms and Conditions
Your access and use of the website is subject to the following terms and conditions ("Terms and Conditions") and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing the website, you accept, without limitation or qualification, the Terms and Conditions below.
License and Website Access
We grant you a limited license to access and make personal use of this website and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of Cuvée Coffee. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this website or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of this website or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This website or any portion of this website may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of Cuvée Coffee. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) without our express written consent. You may not use any meta tags or any other “hidden text” utilizing our name or trademarks without the express written consent of Cuvée Coffee. Any unauthorized use terminates the permission or license granted by Cuvée Coffee.
You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of this website so long as the link does not portray Cuvée Coffee, its affiliates, or their products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive manner. You may not use any
Cuvée Coffee, LLC logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without our express written permission.
Copyright and Trademarks
All content included on this site, including but not limited to, text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio and video clips, digital downloads, data compilations, and software is the property of
Cuvée Coffee, LLC or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of Cuvée Coffee, LLC or its software suppliers and is protected by United States and international copyright laws.
Use of the Website
Please review our Privacy Policy, which also governs your visit to our website, to understand our information practices.
If you use this website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password.
We do sell products for children, but sell them to adults, who can purchase with a credit card. If you are under 18, you may use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Cuvée Coffee, LLC
Beverage Company and its affiliates reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in their sole discretion.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC does not wish to receive any product, marketing, advertising or other ideas that are not covered by issued United States patents or copyrights. If you send any communications or materials to the website by electronic mail or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, suggestions, or the like, all such communications are, and will be treated as, non-confidential and non-proprietary. Anything you transmit or post may be used by
Cuvée Coffee, LLC or its affiliates for any purpose, including, but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast, and posting. Furthermore,
Cuvée Coffee, LLC or its affiliates are free to use, without any compensation to you, any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication you send to the website for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing, and marketing products using such information.
You are prohibited from posting or transmitting any unlawful, threatening, defamatory, libelous, obscene, pornographic or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense or give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any law. You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of any content.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing
Cuvée Coffee, LLC to disclose the identity of anyone posting such materials.
You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate these Terms and Conditions and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify
Cuvée Coffee, LLC or its affiliates for all claims resulting from content you supply. If you do post content or submit material, you grant us and our affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. You grant us and our affiliates and sublicensees the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content, if they choose.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any content posted by you or any third party.
Although
Cuvée Coffee, LLC may from time to time monitor or review discussions, chats, postings, transmissions, bulletin boards and the like on the website,
Cuvée Coffee, LLC is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from the contents of any such communications nor for any error, defamation, libel, obscenity, profanity, or inaccuracy contained in any such communication.
Disclaimers
Your use of the website is at your risk.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy and
Cuvée Coffee, LLC specifically disclaims any liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content on the website. Neither
Cuvée Coffee, LLC nor any other party involved in creating, producing, or delivering the website is liable for any direct, incidental, consequential, indirect, or punitive damages arising out of your access to, or use of, or inability to use or access, the website. Without limiting the foregoing, everything on the website is provided to you "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. Please note that some jurisdictions may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so some of the above exclusions may not apply to you. Check your local laws for any restrictions or limitations regarding the exclusion of implied warranties.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC assumes no responsibility, and shall not be liable for, any damages to, or viruses that may infect, your computer equipment or other property on account of your access to, use of, or browsing in the website or your downloading of any materials, data, text, images, video, or audio from the website.
Descriptions of Products and Services
The website refers to products and/or services that are generally available for purchase in the continental United States but may not be available in your particular locality. The reference to any such products or services in this website does not imply or warrant that these products or services will be available at any time in your particular locality. You should therefore check with your local
Cuvée Coffee, LLC authorized representative for specific product/service availability in your locality.
We do not warrant that the descriptions or other content of this site are accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free. Features and specifications of products described or depicted on the website are subject to change at any time without notice.
Third Party Websites
Cuvée Coffee, LLC is not responsible for the content of any site linked to or from the website. Your linking to any other site is entirely at your own risk. While Cuvée Coffee, LLC may provide links on this website to other sites, the inclusion of such links is for your convenience only and should not be interpreted as an endorsement of the owner/sponsor of the site or the content of the site.
Cuvée Coffee, LLC disclaims all warranties, express and implied, as to the accuracy, validity, legality or otherwise of any materials or information contained on such sites.
Revisions
Cuvée Coffee may at any time revise these Terms and Conditions by updating this posting. Since you are bound by these Terms and Conditions, you should therefore periodically visit this website to review the then current Terms and Conditions.
Severability
If any of these conditions shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that condition shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining condition.
BUY COFFEE
Subscribe
Net Orders Checkout
Item
Price
Qty
Total
Subtotal
Mozambique
Myanmar (Burma)
Namibia
Nauru
Nepal
Netherlands
Netherlands Antilles
New Caledonia
New Zealand
Nicaragua
Zimbabwe
AlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederated States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
Shipping Methods
